Guide to the University of Chicago Department of Anthropology Records 1929-1997
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: Fay-Cooper Cole Papers
  - Philippine Project (University of the Philippines; O. H. Beyer), 1934-1935 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Pond, Alonzo W. 1928-1934 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Provinse, John, 1929-1937 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Provost Marshall Teaching Program, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Faculty, 1944-1945 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Press, U. of C., Contracts for Series in Anthropology, 1935-1941 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Q, Miscellaneous, 1945-1947 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Quimby, George, 1939-1941 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - R, Miscellaneous, 1931-1947 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Race, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Radcliffe-Brown, A. R.1931-1941 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Rainbow Valley Bridge Monument Expedition, 1934-1938 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Rediscovering Illinois: Mailing list, correspondence with press, 1936-1937 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Rediscovering Illinois: Comments and acknowledgements, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Redfiled, Robert, 1929-1933 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Redpath Bureau, 1928-1933 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Riste, Victor, 1933, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller Foundation: Reports and correspondence, 1929-1937 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller Foundation: Leonard Outwaite, 1932-1933 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Roest, P. K., 1928-1933 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Ruyle, J. B. (Illinois State Archaeological Society), 1939-1943 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - S, Miscellaneous, 1940-1947 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - S, Miscellaneous, 1939-1941 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Sapir, Edward, 1930-1934 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Sapir, Edward, 1928-1930 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Science, 1928-1932, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Science Service, 1928-1930, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Scientific American, 1929-1931 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Setzler, Frank, 1928-1944 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Setzler, Frank, 1929-1942 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Shetorne, H. C. (Ohio State Archaeological and Historical Society), 1925-1946 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Social Science Research Committee Reports on Research, 1928-1934 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1937-1940 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1928-1933 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Society for Applied Anthropology: Code of Ethics, 1948-1951 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Spicer, Edward and Rosamond, 1935-1940 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Spier, Leslie: Southwest Journal of Anthropology, 1932-1941 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Spoehr, Alex (including notes on social organization of the Seminole), 1939, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Sroles, Leo (including typescripts of Winnebago interviews, 1938) SEE ALSO Series II Subseries IV, 1938, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Sroles Leo, 1934, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Starr, Frederick, 1932, 1934, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence, 1928-29 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence, 1931 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence, 1933 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence, 1934 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence I, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence II, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence I, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence II, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence I, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence II, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence III, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence I, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence II, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence III, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence, 1945 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - State Museum (Illinois) Correspondence, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Stirling, Matthew, 1930-1931, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Strong, Duncan, 1930-1935, 1940-1941 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - T, Miscellaneous, 1932-1947 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority Project, 1933-1934 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Theatrical Production of "The Coming of Man'' 1929-1931 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Tozzer, A. W., 1928-1946 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - U, Miscellaneous, 1939-1946 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - V, Miscellaneous, 1939-1942 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Van Nostrand Co. (Publishers), 1928-1946 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Viking Fund Seminar on Middle American Ethnology and Social Anthropology, Papers, (mimeographed), 1949. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Viking Fund Seminar on Middle American Ethnology and Social Anthropology, Papers, (Mimeographed), 1949 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Viking Fund Seminar on Middle American Ethnology and Social Anthropology, Papers, (Mimeographed), 1949 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Viking Fund Seminar on Middle American Ethnology and Social Anthropology, Papers (Mimeographed) 1949 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - W, Miscellaneous, 1939-1942 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - W, Miscellaneous, 1939-1949 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - W, Miscellaneous, 1930-1945 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Walker Museum of Paleontology, U. of C., Alfred Romer, 1931 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Warner, W. Lloyd (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Weckler, Joseph (including field material about Spanish-speaking American communities, 1940) 1938-1947 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - White, Leslie, 1940-1942 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Whiteford, Andrew, 1931-1942 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Wisconsin State Historical Society, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Wisdom, Charles, 1936-1943 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Wissler, Clark, 1941-1944 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Y-Z, Miscellaneous, 1940-1947 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Zingg, Bennett (Tarahumara, Mexico, 1930-31), 1930-1931, 1937-1938 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Zingg, Robert, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Zingg, Robert, 1933-1935 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Zingg, Robert, 1935-1936, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Series II: Research
  - Subseries 1: Committee on the Ethno-history of the Upper Mississippi Valley
    - Correspondence I, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence II, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence III, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence I, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence II, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence III, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence IV, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence V, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence VI, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1941-1946 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence II, 1941-1946 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous printed reports, 1938-1939 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Handwritten notes on progress, drafts of reports, etc., 1934, 1938-1939, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - University of Tennessee, Knoxville, Report of J. Joe Finkelstein, 1939, undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 2: Archaeology Summer Research
    - Correspondence and field reports, 1934 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and field reports, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence and field reports, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and field reports I, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and field reports II, 1937 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and field reports I, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence and field reports II, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence and field reports I, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence and field reports II, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence and field reports I, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and field reports II, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence and field reports I, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and field reports II, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and field reports III, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and field reports IV, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence and field reports V, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence and field reports VI, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence and field reports, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence and field reports, 1944 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Pere Marquette State Park, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Pottowattomie Woods Site, 1937-1938 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Ottawa and Savanna, Ill., 1940-1942 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Fisher Site, 1927, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Kankakee Site, 1928-1929 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Lewistown, Ill., 1932 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Winnebago, Wisc.1937 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 3: Archaeology, General
    - Committee on Basic Needs in Archaeology, 1939-1945 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Basic Needs in Archaeology, 1941-1942 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Archaeological sites, correspondence and enquiries regarding, 1927 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Archaeological leads I, 1935-1946 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Archaeological Leads II, 1935-1937 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Leads outside of Illinois, 1935-1942 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Archaeological survey of Illinois, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Pictorial Survey of Mississippi Valley: Thorne Deuel, 1931-1934 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Pictorial Survey of Mississippi Valley: leads, 1931-1937 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Maps (including list of abbreviations of Illinois counties), undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Preservation and care of archaeological materials, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Field methods, records, etc., 1936-1937 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Improved techniques of plaster casting, Oscar Waldemar, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Materials examined by other institutions, 1935-1937 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Committee on Cooperation with the Field Museum, 1930-1933 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Cooperation with the Natural History Museum, undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Spiro, Oklahoma field notes, undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Rock Island county survey, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Adams County Archaeological Survey of Ill., 1929 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1934-1940 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Archaeological Committees, 1935 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Field Conference, July 8-10, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper References, 1926, 1929, 1934, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Enquiries from Amateurs I, 1941-1944 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Enquiries from Amateurs II, 1940-1943 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Enquiries from Amateurs III, 1938-1940 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Enquiries from Amateurs IV, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Enquiries from Amateurs V, 1937-1938 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 4: Rachel Commons - Leo Srole Ho-Chunk (Winnebago) Research
    - Correspondence, 1932-1939 [1994] (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Interviews/Notes #1, 1938, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Interviews/Notes #2, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Interviews/Notes #3, 1927, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Interview Notes, Leo Srole, 1938-1949 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Stories, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Medicine Dance, Commons, 1932 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - War Bundle, Commons and Srole Notes, 1932, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Genealogy, Commons (Srole?), undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Dissertation Outline, Srole, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Peyote, Srole, 1939 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - World War II, Srole, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Land Ownership, (Srole?), 1936,1937, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Winnebago Constitution, 1938, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Indian Claims Legislation, 1911,1931 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Wisconsin Winnebago Census, June 30, 1921 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Wisconsin Winnebago Census, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Winnebago Correspondence, Lurie, Nancy, 1970,1972 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Yellow Thunder Material, undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Ladies Aid Society, Constitution, 1932, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Commons Field Notebooks, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Commons Field Notebooks, 1931, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Commons Field Notebooks, 1932 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Commons, Winnebago Vocabulary and Structure Notebooks, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Commons, Winnebago Glossary and Untitled Notebook, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Series III: Alphabetical Files
  - Subseries 1: Correspondence
    - Correspondence A, 1950-1952 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence B, 1951-1954 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence C, 1950-1953 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence D, 1951-1952 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence E, 1951-1956 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence F, 1949-1954 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence G, 1951-1953 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence H, 1947-1956 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence I, 1951-1956 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence J, 1951-1953 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence K, 1951-1957 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence L, 1951-1953 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence M, 1949-1956 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence N, 1951-1952 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence O, 1951-1953 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence P, 1950-1953 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence Q, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence R, 1951-1956 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence S, 1950-1955 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence T, 1950-1953 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence U, 1951-1953 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence V, 1950-1952 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence W, 1951-1953 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 2: General Alphabetical Files
    - A-General, 1956-1963 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Admissions-Graduate, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Advisor List, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Africa Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - African Studies program, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Agenda- Faculty Meeting (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - American Anthropologist, Book Review Editor, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - AAA, NSF Visiting Lecturers Series, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - American Indian Charter Convention, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Announcements, 1964-1965 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Anthropology Club, 1959-1963 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Anthropology Department Publications, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Anthropology Tomorrow, 1960-1965 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Archeology, 1959, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Assistance For Students, 1955-1956 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Audio-Visual Equipment, 1959-1960 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - B, General, 1957-1962 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Barghoon, Frederick, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Behavioral Sciences, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Books, 1958, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Bookstore, University of Chicago, 1958-1962 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Building and Grounds Orders, 1960-1969 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - C, General, 1957-1968 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Cairo, American University, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Center for Continuing Education, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Center for Programs in Governmental Administration, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Central European Conference, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Central States Anthropological Society, 1962, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Chiapas Project, 1959-1962 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Chicago Anthropologist Newsletter, 1955-1957 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Chicago Anthropologist Newsletter, Contributions, (Current), 1959-1960 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Chicago Anthropology Society, 1959-1960 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Chicago Linguistic Society, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Chicago Service League, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Civilization, Chinese Institute in, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Class Scheduling, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Clinics, University of Chicago, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Collaboration with Escuela Nacional de Antropologia y Historia, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - College, Non-Western Civilization Courses, undated (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - College, Social Sciences Section, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Committee of International Relations, undated (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Committee on Research on Africa and the Near East, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Council of the University Senate, Anthro Representatives, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Crusade of Mercy, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Current Anthropology, 1958-1963 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - D, General, 1957,1959 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Dean of Students, 1961,1964 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Department Dinner and Luncheon Meetings, 1959,1962 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - E, General, 1960, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Educational Policies Committee, undated (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - E and E, 1957,1958 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Exam Schedules, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Extension Program and Courses, 1962,1963 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - F, General, 1958,1959 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Information, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Lists, 1958,1969 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Faculty News Bulletin, 1958,1962 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Seminar (Department of Anthropology), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Faculty/Student Lists, 1950,1959 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Films, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - G, General, 1958,1968 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - H, General, 1957,1969 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Hay, John, Fellows, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Hotel Accommodations, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Housing, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - I, General, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Information Requests, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Information Requests, 1963,1969 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Information, Student, 1956, 1960, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Inquiries, Replies by Staff Members, 1958,1960 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Insurance Information, Reports, 1965, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - International House, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Inter-University Scholars, 1957, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Intra-Departmental, Inter-Departmental, 1959,1961 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - J, General, 1959,1960 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Jobs Requested, 1960,1969 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - K, General, 1957,1966 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Kelley, David, ON the Decipherment of the Maya Glyphs, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Kinship Terms, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Kroeber, Anthropology Society, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - L, General, 1957,1964 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Language Laboratory, 1964,1969 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Library, Anthropology, 1958,1968 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Library Committee, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Library Gifts, 1960,1967 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Library, Harper, 1962,1965 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Library, Maps, 1956,1959 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Library, Schedule, 1966,1969 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Library, Reports, 1961,1968 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Library, University (HRAF File), 1959,1961 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Library of Congress, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Linguistics, 1959,1970 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - M, General, 1958,1968 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - MacMillan Company, Royalty Statements, 1965, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Material for Manual, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Minority Recruitment (Student), 1970 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Moving, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - N-General, 1958-1963 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - NDEA Title IV, Request for Additional Graduate Fellowships, 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - NDEA Title IV, Research and Studies, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - NDEA Title IV, South Asian Studies Program, 1958-1961 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Near PhD's, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - NEA Survey, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - NICH (National Institute of Child Health and Human Development), and HD Research, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - NIH (National Institutes of Health), undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - NIH/NSF Cost of Education Allowance, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - NIMH (National Institute of Mental Health), Information, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - NIMH (National Institute of Mental Health), Miscellaneous, 1961, 1967-1968 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - NORC (National Opinion Research Center), 1967 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - NSF, Application Procedure, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - NSF Fellowship and Award Announcements, 1959-1960, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - NSF, Department Grant Proposal for Graduate Traineeship, 1966-1967 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - NSF, International Studies Building, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - NSF, Research Grant Budget Summary, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - NSF, Stretch Out, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Northwestern University Collaboration, 1959, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - O, General, 1959, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Office Manual, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - P, General, 1958, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Party, March 8, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Petty Cash, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - PhD Thesis Development and Proposal, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - PhD Thesis Committees, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Planning and Development, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Post, doctoral Applicants, 1963, undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - R, General, 1958, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Registrar's Reports, Enrollment Statistics, 1954, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Registrar's Reports, Enrollment Statistics, 1960, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Registrar's Reports, Enrollment Statistics, 1961, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Registrar's Reports, Grade Distribution, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Religion, American Academy of, undated (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Research, Faculty Proposals, 1960, 1962, 1969, undated (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Research, First Draft Proposals, 1953-1957, undated (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Research- Faculty Lists, 1959-1960 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - S, General, 1956-1963 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Secretarial Assistance, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Seminars, 1962-1963 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Service Bureau, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Smithsonian Institution, 1968-1970 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Social Sciences Executive committee (Minutes), 1955-1961 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Social Science Research Council, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Society For Social Research, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Student Faculty Reception Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Student-Faculty Reception, 1966-1967 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Student Journal, undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Student Lists, 1897-1970 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Student Loan Availability, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Student Newsletter, 1969, undated (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Student Organizations, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Student Political Activity, 1968-1969, undated (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Student Suggestions for Departmental Reform, 1969-1970 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Summer Conference, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Summer Fieldwork, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Summer Military Reserve Training, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Surveys, 1968-1969 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Survey, External Research Staff, (State Department), 1963 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Survey, Indirect Time, 1962,1963 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Survey, Indirect Time, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Survey, Keys, 1958, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 9)